uh if you're listening to the radio in
the car you are are going to hear the
country music now I happen to like a lot
of stuff it's just so happy Way Down
Yonder on the chatah ho she never knew
how much a might water meant to me
well looks like I'm having a seizure up
here I think you have to live in the
south to write a song like that I don't
think you could write that song if you
live in Brooklyn way up yonder on the
Hudson River body P are floating right
up next to me well I seen me some tires
and some chemical waste a fish give me
the burden then he spitting my face
there
[Applause]
there who else I like Keith
Urban I love that song I want to love
somebody love somebody like you somebody
like you not
you I also love uh the girl that sings
the Sunday Night Football Song Carrie
underwear
um she had like the biggest country song
like in a decade um some years ago all
the women Know It Before He Cheats right
ladies I'm going to dig my keys into the
side drive all right get over
it I always thought to myself what if it
was reversed what if it was a guy in
that situation whole different
song right now she's probably on the
prowel walking like a cougar wearing
nothing but a towel right now she's
checking out the pool boy thinking that
she might have found herself another
love toy right now she probably at the
gym sweating to the oldies with a
trainer named Tim before get
him I'm going to grab her T and erase
the view make the dog take a dump in her
Jimmy chew shoe you clone's picture is
my new dart
board I'm going to pour Jack danels in a
coffee cup stink up the joh and leave
the toilet seat up maybe next time
she'll think before she
[Music]
cheats there you go
yeah not exactly a love
song I like romance I met a couple once
uh playing Atlantic City they were
married 67 years
and the guy was very sharp he goes I'll
tell you my secret I make all the big
decisions and she makes all the little
decisions he said oh yeah big decisions
like what he goes well we haven't had
any of those
[Music]
yet I know how it works I know how it
works uh I learned everything I'll ever
need to know about marriage from my mom
and dad they were like a TV couple from
the 60s they were like Ralph and Alice
Kramden they'd be in the kitchen and
Mom's like do you want dinner what are
my choices yes or
no dad will be standing there mom walks
out to him what are you doing nothing
you're staring at our Mar certificate
for over an hour I'm looking for an
expiration
date my lovely ladies ladies I love you
I love you I love you I love you I just
don't understand you no you pluck your
eyebrows and then you draw them back in
with a
pencil
who does
that single women single women come home
they look in the fridge boom they go
right to the bed married women they come
home they look in the bed they go right
to the
fridge I'm a married guy I got the one
ring that binds them all uh and I've
been married for a while uh my lovely
wife Kathleen and I just celebrated our
36th wedding
anniversary how about that not bad for
showb marriage you know how we lasted 36
years I've only been home for six of
them she said she scares me no she's
she's half Irish half Sicilian I'm lucky
I'm still
alive doesn't take any crap for me I
remember once I was yelling at her in
the car I was getting pulled over right
and I'm yelling at her right like it's
her fault I'm getting pulled over police
officer goes up to my wife he goes ma'am
does he always speak to you this way she
didn't miss a beat she goes only when
he's
drinking that's that's my
girl yeah yeah yeah she uh she wants me
to watch TV with her she's wanted me she
watched that movie she wanted me to
watch Eat Pray Love yeah you know that's
written by a woman if it was written by
a man drink smoke
fart and I caught her watching T1 and
she's screaming at the TV don't go in
there don't don't go in there and I
looked over it was like it was our
wedding
video she's pretty cool I don't cheat on
her I do not cheat and I'll tell you why
I sleep with a CPAP
machine yeah if you could find a woman
willing to lie next to you in sexy
lingerie while you have a vacuum cleaner
hose attached to your face looking like
you're on life support you don't want to
screw that
up I love her I I love her dearly and
I'm very proud of her for for years and
years uh she's a teacher of special
needs and autistic children which is
great and if we have any teachers in the
audience God Bless you that's a noble
I'm going to when I become president I'm
switching baseball player salaries and
teacher salaries
boom all about the kids uh and I know
how that works too I'm a father uh I'm a
girl Dad I am a girl dad I have three
daughters yep three pretty girls
Courtney Jessica Victoria nice names
thank you none of that Hollywood crap
would they give the kids the weird names
gwineth paltro what you name her first
child Apple who names their kid after a
fruit right what if she had twins hey
nice pair
okay they do grow up fast though man oh
Toddlers todders and dogs we had a big
German shepher and my kids were little
poor dog would come out of the room it's
got necklaces on his face stickers on
his please I'm a dog
then we were try to teach her how to use
a pooper scooper man when I was little
we didn't have pooper scoopers he used
to use a shovel and Dad's nine
iron hey some days we would just use the
nine
iron you have to wait a day or two but
you know how that
works but they're so cute when they're
little aren't they like 5-year-old kids
they say things you would never think of
my wife's clashy a little boy named Nick
Nick was well-dressed one day he's
wearing cologne he's five my wife goes
what kind of colog you're wearing I
don't know my mom takes a magazine and
rubs it on my
neck little girl having a conversation
with her grandmother Grandma how old are
you oh honey I'm so old I don't remember
why don't you look in the back of your
panties mine say 5 to
six little boy in church priest ask him
do you know what the resurrection is um
no but if it lasts longer than 4 hours
you have to call your
doctor
[Applause]
you have any PTA parents in here PJ yeah
they they rope you in to do all the
different chores and all the different
functions my thing is because they know
I'm a comedian they have me read like
The the announcements you know community
bulletin board at the end of the
meetings I actually have some that I've
had to read here you go these are not
real these are real I have not written
these here we go ladies don't forget
about the rumage sale it's a chance to
get rid of of those things not worth
keeping around the house bring your
husbands all right this one's cruel
Weight Watches will meet at 7:00 p.m. in
the church Hall please use the large
double doors at the side
entrance somebody wrote that all right
one more we'll move on there will be a
bean supper on Tuesday evening music
will
follow
that